internationalbloggersassociation.com 2018-11-16

# Membership Requirements, Disclosure and Privacy Policies - International Bloggers’ Association

Here at  **International Bloggers’ Association**  we value and protect your privacy just like we value the work we do in your home.

This policy explains when and why we collect information about you, how we use it, the conditions under which we may disclose it to others and how we keep it secure.

We may change this Policy from time to time, so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you’re happy with any changes. By using our website, you agree to be bound by this Policy.

Any questions regarding this Policy and our privacy practices can be sent via our [Contact Us page](https://www.internationalbloggersassociation.com/contact-us/).

To help navigate this page we have included the links below for your convenience.

Membership Requirements

Disclosure Policy

Privacy Policy

Comment Policy

## Who We Are:

**International Bloggers’ Association** is a group of bloggers dedicated to helping other bloggers grow.  You can learn more about [the services we offer on this page](http://ernspikerwoodworks.com/services/).

Our website address is [https://www.internationalbloggersassociation.com](https://www.internationalbloggersassociation.com/).

* * *

## Membership Requirements

To be a part of the IBA, we ask you to pay a yearly fee of $12 USD via Paypal. Our fee helps our association to serve our outstanding members, like you, and to help us continue to add more resources available to you as a member. Thank you!

**Please note:**

  * Your membership will be automatically renewed each year.
  * You may cancel your membership at any time.
  * Your membership fee is non-refundable.

**To Become or Maintain Membership You Must Agree To These Terms:**

  * Maintain at least one blog on your choice of platform.
  * Not Plagiarize Any Other Sites or Copyrighted Images and Text
  * Remain An Ethical Blogger
  * Abide by [Google’s Guidelines](https://support.google.com/webmasters/answer/35769?hl=en)  for Quality Websites
  * Your Blog cannot contain ANY Adult Content such as Pornography

All sites that are created solely for the purpose of redirection or affiliate marketing will not be considered for membership.

**We want our members to be the best of the best and provide quality content to their users.**

Any time your website violates these terms membership will be canceled.

**Disclaimer:**  International Bloggers’ Association cannot be held responsible for any actions or services offered by our members.

* * *

## Disclosure Policy

This blog is a collaborative blog written by a group of individuals. For questions about this blog, please contact  [admin@internationalbloggersassociation.com](mailto:admin@internationalbloggersassociation.com).

_  
_ This blog accepts forms of cash advertising, sponsorship, affiliate links, or other forms of compensation.

_  
_ The compensation received will never influence the content, topics or posts made in this blog. All advertising is in the form of advertisements generated by a third-party ad network. Those advertisements will be identified as paid advertisements.

_  
_ The owner(s) of this blog is compensated to provide opinion on products, services, websites and various other topics. Even though the owner(s) of this blog receives compensation for our posts or advertisements, we always give our honest opinions, findings, beliefs, or experiences on those topics or products. The views and opinions expressed on this blog are purely the bloggers’ own. Any product claim, statistic, quote or other representation about a product or service should be verified with the manufacturer, provider or party in question.

_  
_ This blog does contain content which might present a conflict of interest. This content will always be identified.

* * *

## Privacy Policy

This privacy policy has been compiled to serve better those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

* * *

### **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog or website?**

When becoming a member, registering on our site, or ordering, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address or other details to help you with your experience.

* * *

### **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, become a member, or enter information on our site.

* * *

### **How do we use your information?  **

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•**  To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

**•**  To improve our website in order to better serve you.

**•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

**•**  To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

**•**  To quickly process your transactions.

**•**  To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

* * *

### **How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

**We use regular Malware Scanning.**

We do use an SSL certificate.

* * *

### **Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes, as part of trying to serve you better, we have implemented Google Demographics and Interests Reporting. Please see below for more details on this service.

­

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled that make your site experience more efficient, and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still become a member.

We compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

* * *

### **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise, transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

* * *

### **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

* * *

### **Google**

We use Google Analytics on our website.

**We have implemented the following:**

**•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt-out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt-out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser add-on.

* * *

### **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

**According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

**•**  On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

**•**  By logging in to their account

* * *

#### **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

* * *

#### **Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?**

It’s important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

* * *

### **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

* * *

#### **Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

**•**  We will notify the users via email

**•**  Within 7 business days

**•**  We will notify the users via in-site notification

**•**  Within 7 business days

**•**  We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

* * *

### **CAN-SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

**•**  Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**•**  Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.

**•**  We may also send you additional information related to your product and/or service.

**•**  Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

**To be in accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

**•**  NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

**•**  Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

**•**  Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

**•**  Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

**•**  Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

**•**  Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails:**

**•**  Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email, and we will promptly remove you from  **ALL**  correspondence.

* * *

## Comment Policy

As owner(s) of this site, we reserve the right to remove any comment as find inappropriate. First off, this is a family-friendly site, and comments must be in compliance with that.

**Examples of will not be approved:**

  * Spam comments
  * Harmful comments
  * Comments linking to an inappropriate site
  * Comments with profanity
  * Inappropriate Media
  * Affiliate Links

This is a guideline for you to use as an example of what not to use and does not cover every type of comment that is unacceptable.

* * *

### **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

International Bloggers Association

PO Box 193

Elizabethtown, KY 42702

USA

Last Edited on 2016-03-01
